Ranma of the Saotome School
of Anything Goes Martial Arts.
Oh, yeah!
- Win.
- Oh, yeah!
From Tendo Dojo, Akane Tendo.
- Win.
- That was easy!
These two teens were arranged
to be married by their parents.
You're not the boss of me.
How annoying!
But Ranma suffers
with a small problem.
Whenever he's splashed with cold water,
he transforms into a girl.
NEW GAME - CONTINUE
RANMA1/2
THE HUNTER
There is a wild boar!
Huge boar coming this way!
Here.
Help me! Help!
- Huh?
- Hey, look out!
It's coming! Run away!
He stopped that boar in its tracks
with just a single hand.
Whoa.
Wow.
This fella's something else.
Incredible.
- Are you a martial artist?
- Amazing.
Have you been holing up
in the mountains to train?
I'm trying to find Furinkan High School.
Furinkan High School you say?
Oh. Let me take a look at your map there.
Huh. Hmm?
Hmm. Wait, isn't this a map of Tokyo?
This is Shikoku, friend. Yeah.
Is that right? Then, I'll be off.
He must be lost.
Ranma Saotome, I'm coming to find you.
NO ENTRY FOR LOST TRAVELERS
It's time to fight this out man-to-man.
You should know better
than to try and hide from me!
ANYTHING GOES MARTIAL ARTS
TENDO DOJO
Ranma, please. You have to wait.
No way, absolutely not.
Give it up already.
There's no way you're gonna put me
in girls' clothes.
But all of your clothing is still
in the laundry right now, Ranma.
And the bath is almost ready.
You can't wander all over the house
with your business out.
- Come on!
- You're a guest here. Got it?
Okay, but remind me why
it has to be my clothes that he puts on.
I'm not gonna wear a skirt,
so don't even bother asking.
You don't even know
what we're gonna give you.
Oh, okay, how about these?
Mm-hmm. That looks cute on you.
Wow, that's perfect.
You sure about that? 'Cause it's kinda
feeling a little tight on the boobies.
Really? What about the waist?
Sorta baggy.
All right, Ranma!
You stop it.
Two young ladies should not be fighting.
Well, too bad. I'm a guy!
Do you know
where Furinkan High School is?
You've come all the way out to Hokkaido.
ONE WEEK LATER
- Look.
- Huh?
Well, that's weird.
What's up with that guy?
You there.
What do you want?
Do you know where Furinkan High School is?
Huh?
FURINKAN HIGH SCHOOL
Hmm?
Where can I find Ranma Saotome?
Oh. Over there.
Ranma, wait for me.
Kasumi asked us
to go shopping, remember?
And why do I have to go with you?
'Cause you have to help me
carry back rice and miso.
What's the matter? I thought you'd want
to prove how stupid strong you are.
What did you say to me?
Gonna have to catch me first!
Hmm? Bloodlust?
Ranma, get ready!
- Huh?
- Whoa.
Hmm?
What gives?
Running away just like you always do, huh?
Ranma.
Do you know him?
Mmm?
- Hmm.
- Hmm?
Mm-hmm.
Oh, yeah! You're, uh... the, uh...
Uh.
That brain's really working overtime, huh?
You're...
Allow me to ask one thing, Ranma.
Why did you no-show
when it came time for us to fight?
Oh! I remember now.
I think you and I used to go
to the same school before.
Ryoga Hibiki!
How you doing, man?
You will answer the question!
I waited around for you
at the spot we were supposed to meet
for, like, three days, bro.
Three days?
Yes.
But when I was finally able
to make it there on day four,
I looked and you were nowhere to be found.
All right then. I want to ask you
a question too, Ryoga.
RYOGA'S HOUSE - EMPTY LOT
FOR FIGHT - RANMA'S HOUSE
Could you tell me how it took you
four whole days to get there?
You shut your mouth!
Do you think I was spending
those four days of my life
gaily skipping all over the place?
Aw, son, this is Enoshima.
You're in Harajuku, man.
Are you an idiot? This is Asakusa.
Do you have any real idea
of what I had to overcome to get here?
A crappy sense of direction?
That's what it looks like to me.
Mm-hmm. Yeah, his direction is pretty bad.
You've broken
a gentleman's agreement.
And then you ran away with your dad
to cower in China!
Let's get to the point.
You want to try and find a way
to settle this.
To settle this?
Not even close.
I'm here to get revenge!
Oh.
Hmm?
I don't even care what the cost is to me.
I'll do anything it takes
to wipe out your joy.
CHALLENGE
A letter of challenge?
I've made it official.
Don't run away from me this time.
That guy really hates me.
Huh? Am I happy about anything?
How am I supposed to know if you're happy?
Ranma, I'll find a way
to get my revenge.
My life has gotten so far past the point
of messed up and it's all your fault.
Just like this fragile walnut...
...I'll take your windpipe
into my hands.
And crush it!
Ready yourself, Ranma!
So he's challenging you, huh?
What did you do
to make him want to fight you so bad?
That's a good question.
Hmm.
Oh, where are my keys?
- Hang on to this for me.
- Hmm?
We're back.
We got the stuff.
A FEW DAYS LATER
Thanks for making food!
Uh.
You ass!
Fork over the sausage!
Can't you let us eat our breakfast
in peace?
- Animal! Just stick to bamboo!
- Oh, Ranma.
I think you left this on top of the miso.
Oh. Oh, I did?
Sorry, you were challenged
to a duel. Again?
What did you do this time?
That's the thing. I can't remember.
It must be bad, right?
It can't have been just anything.
He was really angry.
- Oh!
- You figured it out?
Here we go. It's all coming back to you.
I think something happened
at the beginning of the semester.
Time for lunch, boys!
CAFETERIA
Hurry up!
What food have you got? Please!
Okay! I got the last curry bun we have
right here.
Come here!
Next, we got
lots of red bean buns here!
Who wants a red bean bun?
You cad. What is it they call you?
Hmm? Ranma Saotome.
Ranma Saotome.
My curry bun grudge will never die!
I'm pretty sure he was crying
from how frustrated he was.
I mean, lunchtime was
always kind of a war zone.
It was an all-boys' school.
- Boys' school?
Back then, I was a boy
a hundred percent of the time!
Every single day of the year!
Okay. But all of this
over one curry bun?
I know, right?
If that's all...
Hmm. Oh!
All right, you animals.
Here comes the last yakisoba bun!
I guess it was more than once.
Heads up!
Here's the last croquette bun!
Or maybe when--
Melon buns!
Katsu sandwich!
Meat bun!
Oh, and I guess there was
also the seaweed bun.
Hmm.
So it was
a lot of little things that piled up.
Hmm?
Hang on, Ranma.
The date of the challenge was yesterday.
Huh? I wouldn't worry about it.
That guy has no sense of direction at all.
I betcha he's lost right now.
It's this way to Tokyo, right?
No, I just told you it's this way.
What possessed you to go that way?
Just you wait, Ranma Saotome.
ONE WEEK LATER
It's time for the season
with crystal-clear skies
and light, pleasant breezes.
Hello to all you
Furinkan High School students.
We've all been gathered at school field 2,
where Ranma Saotome of the Saotome School
of Anything Goes Martial Arts
is about to face off against a mysterious
stranger claiming to be a student.
We haven't even started,
but the glares on their faces
have been fierce.
It evokes images of historic fights
like Ganryujima.
- What fate will befall our challengers?
- Shut up!
All we can do is hold our breath
and wait to see what will happen.
You're currently listening
to live commentary
brought to you by the Radio Club,
produced and narrated by me, Ichiro.
Ranma. I see you didn't run away
like a coward this time.
Easy there, Ryoga. I didn't come here
'cause I wanted to fight you.
I got you these.
CURRY BUN
What on earth...
So we good?
It's all just water under the bridge now.
Enough with the jokes!
Man, you're just getting greedy now.
Here you go.
Yakisoba bun!
Here's a croquette bun,
a melon bun and a katsu sandwich.
A meat bun and...
...a seaweed bun.
How's that?
I don't think I forgot anything, did I?
What kind of game are you playing
with me, you bastard?
I thought this was
'cause you were mad about your buns.
Who in the world would fight over buns?
- Oh.
- Why bother spending money on these
if they're all gonna be
past their expiration date?
Well, yeah, 'cause I had to wait
for you to show up for a week.
Enough. Let's go!
Uh.
Chill out a sec.
Just tell me why first.
I had to make my way through hell
and it's all your fault!
Yeah, I still don't get it.
- Hmm.
- No, of course you don't.
And even if I did try tell you the reason,
you wouldn't believe me to begin with.
Mmm?
Hmm? Hmm?
Mmm.
You won't be able to scurry away
from me now, Ranma!
Ryoga.
How...
How many bandanas are you wearing?
That's the question
you wanna ask right now?
He can't get away now!
This match looks
like it's gonna be a close one.
Why is this thing so heavy?
I don't think I could lift it.
Let me try.
I'm pretty sure
that thing made me throw my back out.
How can he
just throw around something this heavy?
He's on a
whole different level than Ranma.
How are you feeling right now?
Ranma, wait! You need
more space between you!
It won't end well if he lands a hit!
Huh?
Ha!
Okay.
Let's see what happens
when I make you bring your A-game.
Ranma! This guy's no joke.
His arms are monsters!
It took you this long to figure it out.
So, Ryoga? How you wanna handle this?
Do you think this is a joke?
- I refuse to crawl...
- Mm-hmm.
...on all fours
...like a dog!
A one-armed spring into the air!
Whoa, there!
He's coming this way!
- Take this!
-!
Huh?
You didn't have to destroy
my favorite shirt.
I don't want to waste time talking about
girlie stuff in the middle of a fight!
Who says
liking clothes is girlie?
Ryoga!
- He's jumped over the fence!
- Follow him!
I want you to take it back.
Take it back now!
Whoa!
What just happened? A pillar of water has
sprung up like a geyser.
Ranma.
Let's go!
Huh? Wha... Wait a mi--
Where did you come from?
Come on! Get your head back in the game!
Wha... Ranma?
Who else could I possibly be,
you stupid idiot?
Careful, Ranma. Your chest!
Huh?
Did you really not notice
that you'd turned into a girl?
R-Ranma. So then you're...
Go ahead and laugh
if you think it's so funny.
I have no idea what I could've done
that made you hate me so much.
But I'm trying.
Whatever this body does, I just want
to live a happy and honest life.
Hmm.
Oh. Huh?
Ha!
Is this really
all that there is to your misery?
Especially when you look
as cute as you do.
You believe
your tale of woe will dissuade me?
Don't make me laugh!
Uh-oh. We're seeing the beginnings
of a fierce battle ahead.
Wha... Something is flying this way!
Is it a bird? Or a plane?
No, it's a bandana!
I'll go get hot water.
You idiot. You'll get yourself hurt.
I'll be okay.
You're open!
What will you do now?
Even if you dodge the umbrella,
I'll use these bandanas
to attack you from every direction!
Okay, hold on tight. Ready?
The skill!
Even while holding such heavy weapons,
the combatants are leaping in the air
like dancers!
Running away, you coward?
Uh, just give me a second.
Uh...
- Nice job!
- That was ju--
Uh, what's going on?
What do you mean?
This is all your fault, you know.
Nobody asked you to get involved.
Oh, yeah? Well there's no way
you would've beat him as a girl.
- You know that.
- That's a pretty messed-up thing to say.
This battle was supposed to be
a man-to-man before you poked in.
How exactly are you a man?
Oh, look. What could he be doing now?
- ...work this out for you.
- Huh?
Ah, just shut up!
You always do this.
It's like you need to stick your nose
in other people's--
If you were a little more cautious--
Let me go.
Are you serious?
I'm not holding you
because I like it, idiot.
Oh.
If my worrying about you is gonna be
that annoying,
fine, then.
Akane.
We're not finished yet!
Shut up!
Akane.
Uh... Um...
I don't care.
From now on, I don't want to have
anything to do with you anymore.
Uh...